// flashcards/fars.js
export const fars = [
  { front: "121.593", back: "Authority to Dispatch (Intermediate Stop Without Redispatch Rule)" },
  { front: "121.599", back: "Weather Conditions Familiarity Requirements" },
  { front: "121.601", back: "Required Information From Dispatcher to PIC (Weather)" },
  { front: "121.609", back: "Communications and Navigation Equipment/Facilities Requirements" },
  { front: "121.617", back: "Departure/Takeoff Alternates" },
  { front: "121.619", back: "Destination Alternates: The “1-2-3” Rule" },
  { front: "121.621", back: "Destination Alternate Requirements (“The Island Rule”)" },
  { front: "121.625", back: "Alternates: Weather Minimums" },
  { front: "121.627", back: "Continuing Flight in Unsafe Conditions" },
  { front: "121.631", back: "Original Dispatch or Flight Release, Redispatch, or Amendment of Dispatch or Flight Release (“Pen & Ink”)" }
];